Guide to the Marketing Office, Yale School of Drama, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Marketing Office, Yale School of Drama, records
1973-2008
RU 933
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
13.75
The records consist of marketing and publicity files, including press releases, clippings, photographs, posters, programs and newsletters documenting productions of the Yale School of Drama and the Yale Repertory Theatre.
Yale School of Drama
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-E (YRG 22-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
The records partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of marketing and publicity files, including press releases, clippings, photographs, posters, programs and newsletters documenting productions of the Yale School of Drama and the Yale Repertory Theatre.
College theater; Repertory theater; Theater management; Theater programs; Theater -- Public relations; Theatrical posters, American; Photographs; Playbills; Yale Repertory Theatre; Yale School of Drama
- Publicity materials from the Marketing Office, 1975-2001; Accession 2003-A-155
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Yale Repertory Theatre
    - General Features
      - 1995 Jan - May (Box 1)
      - 1994 May - Dec (Box 1)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre /Yale School of Drama print ads
    - Betty's Summer Vacation; Serious Money; Iphegenia of Aulis; Three Sisters; The Trial, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - You Never Can Tell; Kingdom of Earth; It Pays to Advertise, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre
    - Print Ad Clippings Season, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
    - Press Clippings
      - 2001 May - Jul (Box 1)
      - 2001 Jan - Feb (Box 1)
      - 2001 Mar - Apr (Box 1)
      - 1997 May - 1998 May (Box 2)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 2)
      - First lady; Cryptogram; Triumph of Love (Box 2)
      - Skin of our Teeth; Amy Bock; Thunder Knocking, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Tony Award presented to Yale, Press Clippings Slide and Program, 1991 (Box 2)
  - General Press Features, 1992 April 29 - 1994 May (Box 2)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre
    - Newsletters
      - 1985-1991 (Box 2)
      - 1975-1985 (Box 2)
    - General Press Clippings
      - 1997 Jan - Sep (Box 3)
      - 1996 Jun - Dec (Box 3)
    - Reviews and Features
      - Slavs; Uncle Vanya; Le Bourgeois Avant Garde; Special Events, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
      - Antigone in NY; Figaro/Figaro; Twelfth Night, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
      - Mump and Smoot; The School for Wives; Special Events, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
      - The America Play; As you Like It, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
      - Oleanma; The Green Bird, 1993-1994 (Box 3)
    - Programs, photographs, reviews, features, study guides
      - The First Lady, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - The Cryptogram, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - Triumph of Love, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - The Skin of our Teeth, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - The Adventures of Amy Bock, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - Thunder Knocking on the Door, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre architecture photos and articles (Box 5)
  - Subscription renewal campaign
    - FY 1994-FY 1996 (Box 5)
    - FY 1989-FY 1993 (Box 5)
  - Yale School of Drama
    - As you Like It programs, poster, photos, press releases, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - CWP's posters/programs, 1994-1995 (Box 5)
  - CWP posters/programs, 1995-1999 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1987-1999 (Box 5)
  - Yale School of Drama
    - Subscription campaign
      - 1985-1994 (Box 6)
      - 1980-1985 (Box 6)
    - Program info/application
      - 1981-1989 (Box 6)
      - 1989-2000 (Box 6)
  - Photographs
    - Landscape of the Body, Venus, Beaux Strategem, Mrs. Warrens Profession, Pentecost, le Cirque Invisible, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Geography II: Tree, A cup of Coffee, Richard III, Imaginary Invalid, Betrayal, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - Galileo, The Glass Menagerie, Crumbs from the Table of Joy, Peter and Wendy; Measure for Measure, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Big Night, The Birds, Mump and Smoot, Rice Boy, Curse of the String Class, 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - The Colored Museum; My Children, My Africa; The Beauty part; Edward II; On the Verge, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
    - Hamlet; St. Joan of the Stockyard; Escape from Happiness; The Baltimore Waltz, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
    - Oleanna; As you Like it; The Green Bird; School for Wives; The American Play, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
    - Le Bourgeois Avent Garde; Figaro/Figaro; Twelfth Night; Slavs!; Antigone in NY; Uncle Vanya, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre
    - Press Clippings:
      - Various, 1999-2000 (Box 8)
      - Various, 1999-2001 (Box 8)
      - General, 2000 (Box 8)
      - General, 1999 (Box 9)
      - The Beaux Stratagem; Venus; Landscape of the body; Special Events, 1996 (Box 9)
  - O'Neil Theatre Center: national playwrights Conference Programs (Box 9)
  - Helen Hayes Awards (Box 9)
  - Yale Rep Awards/Citations, Articles, Photos; etc. (Box 9)
  - Stan Wojewodski Jr. News Clippings (Box 10)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre
    - Programs, press releases, etc
      - Imaginary Invalid; Betrayal; A Cup of Coffee; Richard III; Geography II: Tree, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
      - Peter and Wendy; Galileo; Crumbs from the Table of Joy; Measure for Measure; The Glass Menagerie; White Oak Dance, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
    - Press Clippings; Le Cirque Unvisible; Pentecost; Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1996 (Box 10)
- Publicity materials from the Marketing Office, 1973- 2001; Accession 2005-A-034
  - The Crazy Locomotive, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Mump and Smoot, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - Geography Slides (Box 1)
  - Yale Cabaret Flyers, 1987-1990 (Box 1)
  - Geography Program, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Saint Joan of the Stockyards program, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - American Theatre Magazine, 1994 March (Box 1)
  - American Theatre Magazine, 1987 January (Box 1)
  - Theater Week Education Issue, 1993 October 18 (Box 1)
  - Slides from White Oak Dance Project (Baryshnikov), 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Two Trains Running Program (Box 1)
  - The Piano Lesson Photos (Box 1)
  - Fences Photos (Box 1)
  - Henry Winkler Photos for A&E: Biography (Box 1)
  - Splash Hatch on the E Going Down photos (Box 1)
  - Fences program (Box 1)
  - Two Trains Running photos (Box 1)
  - Slides from The Piano Lesson, Long Days, Troilus and Cressida, A Lesson from Aloes, A Cup of Coffee, Mrs. Warrens, Landscape of the Body, Underground, and Moon over Miami (Box 1)
  - The Fabulous Invalid Photo (Box 1)
  - The Death of the last Black Man Ever photos (Box 1)
  - Cast photos and Negatives (unknown plays and years) (Box 1)
  - The Frogs negatives, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Slides from The American Play, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Betrayal slides, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - The Skriker, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - Priority Brochure Slides from years, 1979-1992 (Box 1)
  - Negatives from Electra, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Negatives from Medea, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Negatives from Measure for Measure, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Negatives from Dragon, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Photographs
    - Adventures of Amy Bock (Box 1)
    - Moon over Miami, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - Troilus and Cressida (Box 1)
    - Rococo, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Pictures of Moon for the Misbegotten (Box 1)
    - We bombed in New Haven, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Watergate Classics, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
    - The Idiots Karamazov, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Mistaken Identities, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - The Tempest, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
    - The Government Inspector (Box 1)
    - Headshot of Jane Kaczmarak (Box 1)
    - Moon over Misbegotten (Box 1)
    - Mrs. Warren's Profession (Box 1)
    - Triolus and Cressida (Box 1)
    - John Turturro (Box 1)
    - In the Clap Shack proofs, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
    - Heaven, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - The Birds, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - Big Night, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - Caucasian Chalk Circle, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
    - Democracy in America (Box 2)
    - Slavs! (Thinking about the Longstanding Problems of Virtue…) (Box 2)
    - Pentecost (Box 2)
    - Adventures of Amy Bock (Box 2)
    - The Glass Menagerie (Box 2)
    - Triumph of Love (Box 2)
    - A Place With the Pigs (Box 2)
    - Search and Destroy (Box 2)
    - Kiss of the Spiderwoman (Box 2)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (Box 2)
    - Ma Rainey… (Box 2)
    - Ivanov (Box 2)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (Box 2)
    - The Frogs, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - Two Trains Running (Box 2)
    - The Piano Lesson (Box 2)
    - Moon over Miami (Box 2)
    - Dynamite Tonight! (Box 2)
    - Le Bourgeois Avant-Garde, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
    - Venus (Box 2)
    - Triumph of Love (Box 2)
    - Ah! Wilderness (Box 2)
    - The Ghost Sonata, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
    - Triolus and Cressida (Box 2)
    - Ma Rainey (Box 2)
    - Resurrection of Lady Lester (winter fest), 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - Slavs (Box 2)
    - Pentecost (Box 2)
    - Amy Bock (Box 2)
    - Triumph of Love (Box 2)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1999
    - Place with the Pigs (Box 2)
    - Kiss of the Spider Woman (Box 2)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night (Box 2)
    - Ma Rainey, 198/1984 (Box 2)
    - Two Trains Running (Box 2)
    - Fences (Box 2)
    - August Wilson and Lloyd Richards on set of Fences (Box 2)
    - The Piano Lesson (Box 2)
    - Joe Turner's Come and Gone (Box 2)
  - Posters
    - Oversize
      - The Duchess of Malfi (Box 3)
      - Imperceptible Mutabilities (Box 3)
      - The Art of Success (Box 3)
      - The Misanthrope (Box 3)
      - Romeo and Juliet (Box 3)
      - As You Like It (Box 3)
      - The Prince of Hamburg (Box 3)
      - The Blind (Box 3)
      - The Great Highway (Box 3)
      - The Tragedy of Hamlet, Prince of California (Box 3)
      - Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights (Box 3)
      - King John / As You Like It (Box 3)
      - The Three Sisters (Box 3)
      - Fuente Ovejuna (Box 3)
      - The Dragon (Box 3)
      - Twelfth Night (Box 3)
      - Poster Crazy Locomotive (Box 3)
      - Poster Mr. Puntila and his Chauffer Matty, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
      - The wild Duck, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
      - Mistaken Identities, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
      - As you Like it, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
      - Titus Andronicus (Box 3)
      - Sainte Carmen of the Main (Box 3)
      - Pericles (Box 3)
      - Mississippi Nude (Box 3)
      - Nabo (Box 3)
      - Richard III (Box 3)
      - Good Person of Szechwan (Box 3)
      - Don Juan (Box 3)
      - Pacific Overtures (Box 3)
      - Special Events: Hazelle Foodman; Shut Up and Love Me; Astrid Hadad (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous Other: The Piano Lesson, A Lesson From Aloes, and Master Harold. (Box 3)
      - Figaro/Figaro, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
      - YRT/YSD Season 1998-2000 (Box 4)
      - Dangerous Border Game (Box 4)
      - Happy End (Box 4)
      - Pope and the Witch (Box 4)
      - Ride Across Lake Constance (Box 4)
      - Love of 3 Oranges (Box 4)
      - Don Byron Scar of Shame (Box 4)
      - Diva Studies, 1996 (Box 4)
      - Pilgrims of the Night (Box 4)
      - Good Person of Szechwan (Box 4)
      - Waiting for Godot (Box 4)
      - Tom's Suite, 1991-1992 (Box 4)
      - Name of Oedipus Jocasta, 1991-1992 (Box 4)
      - Hamlet (Box 4)
      - Stage Door (Box 4)
      - Great Men of Science, 1991-1992 (Box 4)
      - Amnestia, 1991-1992 (Box 4)
      - Revizor, 1997 (Box 4)
      - Seagull, 1997 (Box 4)
      - Le Bourgeois Avant Garde, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
      - Le Cirque Invisible, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
      - Pentecost, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
      - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1995-1996
      - The Beaux Stratagem, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
      - Venus, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
      - Landscape of the Body, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
      - The First Lady, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - The Cryptogram, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - Triumph of Love, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - The Adventures of Amy Bock, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - Thunder Knocking on the Door, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      - Geography, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
      - Candida, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
      - Splash Hatch on the E Going Down, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
      - A Midsummer's Night Dream, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
      - The Cure at Troy, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
      - Petersburg, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
      - Twelfth Night, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
    - Folio
      - Winterfest 9: Starting Monday, Phaedra and the Hippolytus, The Beach, Interrogating of the Nude, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
      - Winterfest 8: Neddy, The Wall of Water, The My House Play, Chute Roosters, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
      - Winterfest 10: Daylight in Exile, Poster Pill Hill, Rust and Run, Dinosaurs, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
      - Winterfest 5, 6 (Box 5)
      - Sarcophagus, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
      - The Piano Lesson, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
      - Melons, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
      - The Miser, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
      - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
      - Ah, Wilderness!, 1987-1988
      - Intermezzo, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
      - Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
      - The Alchemist, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
      - Moon over Miami, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
      - Cobb, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
      - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
      - The Solid Gold Cadillac, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
      - Miss Julie, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
      - Warrior Ants, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Summer and Smoke, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
      - Troilus and Cressida, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
      - Two Trains Running, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
      - Pygmalion, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
      - Ivanov, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
      - Largo Desolato, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      - Underground, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      - Scapin, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      - Moon for the Misbegotten, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
      - Cherry Orchard (Box 11)
      - On the Verge, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- Marketing Office records, 1996-2008; Accession 2009-A-029
  The materials are restricted until Jan 1, 2044.
  - Procurement Web Requisitions (Project X Training), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Internet Marketing Manager, Spring 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Asst. Marketing Director (New Media) Final Report, Fall 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student Passbooks Sales Report, Fall 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - YRT Telemarketing Campaign, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Tickets.com Marketing v5.x Training Manual (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Student Pass Brochures and Postcards, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Pope and the Witch Marketing Binder (YSD), 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Skriker Marketing Binder (YSD), 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle Marketing Binder (YSD), 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - The Master and Margarita Marketing Binder (YSD), 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
  - Astrid Hadad y Los Tarzanes Marketing Binder, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Our Town Marketing Binder (YSD), 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Trial Marketing Binder (YSD), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Three Sisters Marketing Binder (YSD), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire Marketing Binder (YSD), 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - Alcestis Marketing Binder (YSD), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
  - Changes of Heart Marketing Binder (YSD), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Orpheus Descending Marketing Binder (YSD), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth Marketing Binder (YSD), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The Lonesome West Marketing Binder (YSD), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Uncle Vanya Marketing Binder (YSD), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)